http://www.unlocks.co.uk/privacy

Unlocks Privacy & Cookies Policy
Cookies Policy
The Unlocks site uses cookies. By using the Unlocks site and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text file that is stored on your device when you visit a website. Unlocks use both session cookies and persistent cookies on this website. A session cookie is stored on your device and deleted when the broswer is closed or when you manually delete the cookie. A persistent cookie is stored on your device and will be deleted only after a specified time or when you manually deletes the cookie. For more information about cookies, including how to see and control what cookies are stored on your device, please see THIS ARTICLE.
How Unlocks Uses Cookies
Cookies set by Unlocks do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that Unlocks stores about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. Unlocks may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes:
To recognise your device when you visit our website
To track you as you navigate our website
To improve the website's usability
To analyse your use of our website
Blocking Cookies
Details of how to block cookies can be found in the documentation or help files that came with your browser or HERE, however you should be aware that blocking cookies could affect your usability of the Unlocks site.
Contact Unlocks
If you have any questions relating to cookies or the Unlocks Cookie Policy, please Contact Us.
Privacy Policy
Unlocks will not knowingly pass on customer or site visitor details to any third parties. Unlocks will take all reasonable care to ensure that any details submitted through our web forms are kept secure. The details that you submit to Unlocks are kept only to process orders. You have the right to withhold personal information from Unlocks that is not required as part of a transaction.
You can request a copy of any information Unlocks may hold about you by sending an official request letter to Unlocks.
If you find any inaccuracies, they will be deleted or corrected promptly by Unlocks at your request. Any personal information Unlocks may hold will be held securely.
Unlocks will not contact you via email to notify you about important functionality changes to the Unlocks web site, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable unless you have given Unlocks explicit permission to do so.
You have the right to refuse any marketing e-mail from Unlocks.
Unlocks monitors website traffic patterns and usage to help us develop the design and layout of the Unlocks website.
Unlocks may use technology to track the patterns and behavior of visitors to the Unlocks website. This can include using a cookie which would be stored on your computer. You can modify your browser settings to prevent this happening and details of how to do this can be found in your browser documentation or help files.
The information collected by Unlocks in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. If you have any questions about our privacy policy you can Contact Us.
Your statutory rights are not affected by the Unlocks privacy policy.
Need help? Existing customers can check the status of an order, or request support here.
SIM unlocking codes are available for all of the following makes:
